KARAN KUMAR KHARTI

FRONT-END DEVELOPER & DESIGNER













I am a professional Front-end Developer with an experience of 2+ years under my belt. I started programming from the age of 15, fascinated by the fact how a little piece of code can change human life to that extent. My core expertise are HTML, CSS, JavaScript, jQuery, ReactJS, and MERN Stack Development. Apart of my technical skills I am a self-taught Pianist.

I am always in the search of a platform where I can utilize 100% of my skills and learn new things.

EDUCATION

B.Sc Information Technology

QUEST, Nawabshah 2018 - 2022

Intermediate

BISE, Hyderabad 2016 - 2018

Matriculation

BISE, Hyderabad 2014 - 2016

EXPERTISE

Web Development HTML5

CSS JavaScript BootStrap

ReactJS MERN Stack

FIGMA Adobe Xd Zeplin

Adobe Illustrator Ruby

Adobe Photoshop

EXPERIENCE

Freelancer

https://fiverr.com/karankhatri23 03/2021 - Present

Summer Intern

State Bank of Pakistan 08/2021 - 09/2021 (1.5 Month)

Graphic Desgining Intern

QUEST, Nawabshah 06/2021 (1 Month)

Volunteer Team Member

Technomind-19 (IT Depatement QUEST, Nawabshah) 08/2019 - 09/2019 (1 Month)

ACCOMPLISHMENTS & AWARDS

Portfolio Website

https://karan-khatri.github.io/portfolio 11/2020 - 12/2020 (1 Month)

WordPress (Certificate Course)

DigiSkills PK 05/2020 - 07/2020 (3 Months)

Graphic Desgin (Certificate Course)

DigiSkills PK

08/2019 - 10/2019 (3 Months)